const courseData = [
  {
    physics: {
      subject:"physics",  
      videoTutes: [
        "https://www.youtube.com/embed/MVvHdH6n2VE?si=BNnyCUs9cB2LgMVr",
        "https://www.youtube.com/embed/MVvHdH6n2VE?si=BNnyCUs9cB2LgMVr",
        "https://www.youtube.com/embed/MVvHdH6n2VE?si=BNnyCUs9cB2LgMVr",
      ],
      theoryTutes: {
        title: "Theoretical physics",
        description:
          "Theoretical physics is a branch of physics that employs mathematical models and abstractions of physical objects and systems to rationalize, explain and predict natural phenomena. This is in contrast to experimental physics, which uses experimental tools to probe these phenomena. The advancement of science generally depends on the interplay between experimental studies and theory. In some cases, theoretical physics adheres to standards of mathematical rigour while giving little weight to experiments and observations.[a] For example, while developing special relativity, Albert Einstein was concerned with the Lorentz transformation which left Maxwell's equations invariant, but was apparently uninterested in the Michelson–Morley experiment on Earth's drift through a luminiferous aether.[1] Conversely, Einstein was awarded the Nobel Prize for explaining the photoelectric effect, previously an experimental result lacking a theoretical formulation.[2]",
      },
      quiz:[
        {
            queid:101,
            question:"Light year is a unit of which of these following?",
            options:{
                option1:"distance",//correct
                option2:"time",
                option3:"pressure",
                option4:"power"
            },
            answer:"distance"
        },
        {
            queid:102,
            question:"Which of the following is/are independent of mass during the projectile motion?",
            options:{
                option1:"time of Flight",
                option2:"horizontal Range",
                option3:"maximum Height",
                option4:"all of the above"//correct
            },
            answer:"all of the above"

        },
        {
            queid:103,
            question:"The force acting on a body htmlFor a short time are called as:",
            options:{
                option1:"average force",
                option2:"momentum",
                option3:"impulse",//correct
                option4:"tension"
            },
            answer:"impulse"
            
        },
        {
            queid:104,
            question:"When one body is actually moving over the surface of other body, the friction is known as:",
            options:{
                option1:"kinetic friction",//correct
                option2:"limiting friction",
                option3:"static friction",
                option4:"negative friction"
            },
            answer:"kinetic friction"

        },
        {
            queid:105,
            question:"In which of the following states of matter the Interatomic or intermolecular distance is fixed?",
            options:{
                option1:"solids",//correct
                option2:"liquids",
                option3:"gases",
                option4:"Both a and b"
            },
            answer:"solids"

        },
    ]
    },
  },
  {
    maths: {
      subject:"mathematics",  
      videoTutes: [
        "https://www.youtube.com/embed/MVvHdH6n2VE?si=BNnyCUs9cB2LgMVr",
        "https://www.youtube.com/embed/MVvHdH6n2VE?si=BNnyCUs9cB2LgMVr",
        "https://www.youtube.com/embed/MVvHdH6n2VE?si=BNnyCUs9cB2LgMVr",
      ],
      theoryTutes: {
        title: "Theoretical physics",
        description:
          "Theoretical physics is a branch of physics that employs mathematical models and abstractions of physical objects and systems to rationalize, explain and predict natural phenomena. This is in contrast to experimental physics, which uses experimental tools to probe these phenomena. The advancement of science generally depends on the interplay between experimental studies and theory. In some cases, theoretical physics adheres to standards of mathematical rigour while giving little weight to experiments and observations.[a] For example, while developing special relativity, Albert Einstein was concerned with the Lorentz transformation which left Maxwell's equations invariant, but was apparently uninterested in the Michelson–Morley experiment on Earth's drift through a luminiferous aether.[1] Conversely, Einstein was awarded the Nobel Prize for explaining the photoelectric effect, previously an experimental result lacking a theoretical formulation.[2]",
      },
      quiz:[
        {
            queid:201,
            question:" In triangle ABC, if AB=BC and ∠B = 70°, ∠A will b",
            options:{
                option1:"70°",
                option2:"110°",
                option3:"55°",//correct
                option4:"130°"
            },
            answer:"55°"
        },
        {
            queid:202,
            question:" For two triangles, if two angles and the included side of one triangle are equal to two angles and the included side of another triangle. Then the congruency rule is:",
            options:{
                option1:"SSS",
                option2:"SAS",
                option3:"ASA",//correct
                option4:"none of the above"
            },
            answer:"ASA"

        },
        {
            queid:203,
            question:"A triangle in which two sides are equal is called:",
            options:{
                option1:"scalene triangle",
                option2:"equilateral triangle",
                option3:"isosceles triangle",//correct
                option4:"none of the above"
            },
            answer:"isosceles triangle"
            
        },
        {
            queid:204,
            question:"The angles opposite to equal sides of a triangle are:",
            options:{
                option1:"equal",//correct
                option2:"unequal",
                option3:"supplementary angles",
                option4:"complementary angles"
            },
            answer:"equal"

        },
        {
            queid:205,
            question:"If ABC is an equilateral triangle, then each angle equals to:",
            options:{
                option1:"90°",
                option2:"180°",
                option3:"120°",
                option4:"60°"//correct
            },
            answer:"60°"

        },
    ]
    },
  },
  {
    social: {
      subject:"social",  
      videoTutes: [
        "https://www.youtube.com/embed/MVvHdH6n2VE?si=BNnyCUs9cB2LgMVr",
        "https://www.youtube.com/embed/MVvHdH6n2VE?si=BNnyCUs9cB2LgMVr",
        "https://www.youtube.com/embed/MVvHdH6n2VE?si=BNnyCUs9cB2LgMVr",
      ],
      theoryTutes: {
        title: "Theoretical physics",
        description:
          "Theoretical physics is a branch of physics that employs mathematical models and abstractions of physical objects and systems to rationalize, explain and predict natural phenomena. This is in contrast to experimental physics, which uses experimental tools to probe these phenomena. The advancement of science generally depends on the interplay between experimental studies and theory. In some cases, theoretical physics adheres to standards of mathematical rigour while giving little weight to experiments and observations.[a] For example, while developing special relativity, Albert Einstein was concerned with the Lorentz transformation which left Maxwell's equations invariant, but was apparently uninterested in the Michelson–Morley experiment on Earth's drift through a luminiferous aether.[1] Conversely, Einstein was awarded the Nobel Prize for explaining the photoelectric effect, previously an experimental result lacking a theoretical formulation.[2]",
      },
      quiz:[
        {
            queid:301,
            question:"What is a signed document submitted to an officer regarding his/her personal information?",
            options:{
                option1:"affidavit",//correct
                option2:"declaration",
                option3:"agreement",
                option4:"appeal"
            },
            answer:"affidavit"
        },
        {
            queid:302,
            question:"Berlusconi was the Prime Minister of ________. His company owns TV channels, the most important publishing company, a football club (AC Milan)",
            options:{
                option1:"italy",//correct
                option2:"france",
                option3:"poland",
                option4:"germany"
            },
            answer:"italy"

        },
        {
            queid:303,
            question:"How many numbers of parties are registered with The Election Commission of India?",
            options:{
                option1:"7100 Parties",
                option2:"less than 750 parties",
                option3:"700 parties",
                option4:"more than 750 parties"//correct
            },
            answer:"more than 750 parties"
            
        },
        {
            queid:304,
            question:"Political parties are allotted symbols by_______?",
            options:{
                option1:"the government of India",
                option2:"the constitution of India",
                option3:"the party leaders",
                option4:"the election commission"//correct
            },
            answer:"the election commission"

        },
        {
            queid:305,
            question:"Bahujan Samaj party was founded by_______",
            options:{
                option1:"b r Ambedkar",
                option2:"kanshi ram",//correct
                option3:"mamta banerjee",
                option4:" syama prasad"
            },
            answer:"kanshi ram"

        },
    ]
    },
  },
];

export default courseData